http://www.ocean19.com/privacy-policy/

Try Our Free SEO Audit Tool
Try It Now
Hit enter to search or ESC to close
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for Logical Media Group.
This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:
What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the website, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.
What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.
The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.
How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.
Information Collection, Use, and Sharing
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request.
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.
Your Access to and Control Over Information
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website 312.265.0192.
See what data we have about you, if any.
Change/correct any data we have about you.
Have us delete any data we have about you.
Express any concern you have about our use of your data.
Security
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.
Wherever we collect sensitive information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way.
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.
Updates
Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.
If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (312) 265 0192 or contact us.
Links
This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.
445 W Erie Street Suite 208
Chicago, IL 60654
312-465-2911
sales@logicalmediagroup.com
© 2020 Logical Media Group
Free SEO Audit
Blog
Support
Email Marketing
© 2020 Logical Media Group.
Paid Media
Paid Search
As a premier Google partner, Paid Search has long been one of Logical Media Group’s core competencies. Our robust process and team of experts will help efficiently scale your advertising efforts and accomplish your digital marketing goals.
Learn More About Our Paid Search Strategy
Paid Media Services
Paid Search
Social Media Advertising
Amazon Advertising
Conversion Rate Optimization
SEO
Search Engine Optimization
SEO is foundational aspect of every digital marketing strategy and is a pillar of Logical's expertise. From keyword research, onsite optimizations, reporting, link building to content marketing, our team's full-service approach will improve your organic reach and drive qualified traffic to your website.
Learn More About Our SEO Strategy
Organic Marketing
Search Engine Optimization
Google Analytics Configurations
Email Marketing
Conversion Rate Optimization
Amazon Advertising
Web Design
Contact Us
By clicking "Continue" or continuing to use our site, you acknowledge that you accept our Privacy Policy. We also use cookies to provide you with the best possible experience on our website.
Continue
Warning:
Cannot modify header information - headers already sent by (output started at /home/customer/www/logicalmediagroup.com/public_html/wp-content/themes/salient-child/header.php:1) in /home/customer/www/logicalmediagroup.com/public_html/wp-content/plugins/send-pdf-for-contact-form-7/classes/send-pdf.php on line 1420
